[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The book The Boys of Summer tells the story of this baseball team.", "correct_answer": "The Brooklyn Dodgers", "incorrect_answers": ["The New York Yankees", "The Saint Louis Cardinals", "The Boston Celtics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what part of the apple are the toxic compounds cyanogenic glycosides found?", "correct_answer": "Seeds", "incorrect_answers": ["Flowers", "Skin of the fruit", "Leaves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a group of jellyfish called?", "correct_answer": "bloom", "incorrect_answers": ["herd", "school", "pack"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Irish-born Grammy Award-winning actor played King Arthur in the1967 film Camelot, based on the 1960 Broadway musical.", "correct_answer": "Richard Harris", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Goulet", "Laurence Olivier", "Richard Burton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Announced in 2002, model 6370 was what manufacturers first CDMA2000 1X handset?", "correct_answer": "Nokia", "incorrect_answers": ["Siemens", "Sony Ericsson", "Motorola"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these do manatees use to communicate with their calves and other manatees?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Sounds", "Touch", "Movement"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This world famous building opened in The Bronx in 1923.", "correct_answer": "Yankee Stadium", "incorrect_answers": ["The Top of the Sixes", "The Louis Morris Building", "The Shlump Towers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Freddy Kruegers mother was a nun.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This species, also known as Yaminon, is the largest wombat species on the planet.", "correct_answer": "Northern Hairy-nosed Wombat", "incorrect_answers": ["Northern Hairy-nosed Wombat", "Common Wombat", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What disease do the following famous people share: Menachem Begin, Halle Berry, Carol Channing, Miles Davis, Ella Fitzgerald, Ray Kroc, Arthur Ashe, and Ty Cobb?", "correct_answer": "Diabetes", "incorrect_answers": ["Rheumatic fever", "Irritated  bowel syndrome", "Dyslexia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are no stores of the clothing brand Lacoste in Canada.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what shape is the Spanish dessert Tortell traditionally prepared?", "correct_answer": "O-shape", "incorrect_answers": ["Heart shape", "Fish shape", "Star shape"]}]